{
    "id": "4289a52555c0440189a274ac99754c4c",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have always …………….. play games well.",
            "description": "Can and could have no infinitives or participles. For example, there are no forms like I have could ….",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "been able to",
                "able to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0df4c165840048b496d65affd4a79044"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has always …………….. to do what he wanted.",
            "description": "Can and could have no infinitives or participles. For example, there are no forms like I have could ….",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "been allowed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fffc04a5eab422cb6b952be4d9123e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "One cannot help but …………….. his courage.",
            "description": "The infinitive is used without to in the structure cannot help but..",
            "answers": [
                "to admire",
                "admire"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a761a3d946845fc9d2fd81364c74349"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….do you want a holiday?",
            "description": "We use how much in questions about degree.",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How much",
                "How far"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4cbd7f866654412da93e370c6606fa9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will have tea …………… coffee.",
            "description": "As a preposition, instead is used with of.",
            "answers": [
                "instead",
                "instead of",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fdb28e48f9e476eb995f2f42a4db866"
        },
        {
            "question": "They often go fishing …………….. going to school.",
            "description": "Instead of is used when a person, thing or action replaces another. ",
            "answers": [
                "instead",
                "without",
                "instead of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a90652688f744c3c996bdb2dab908291"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stella often goes to the movies …………… telling her parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "instead",
                "instead of",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "624ef2bd2e224846ad9312cae83f0870"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am interested ……………….. what she did with that money.",
            "description": "Interested + ing and interested + infinitive can both be used to talk about a wish to find out something.",
            "answers": [
                "to find out",
                "in finding out",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1c979e6716014206a30b1fe963cd5e94"
        },
        {
            "question": "At no time …………….. aware of what was happening.",
            "description": "If a negative expression comes at the beginning of a clause, it is usually followed by auxiliary verb + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "was he",
                "he was",
                "has he"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f339e8ee99be4ca6bf6444bef244d0ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only then ………….. understand what he meant.",
            "description": "If a negative expression comes at the beginning of a clause, it is usually followed by auxiliary verb + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "I did",
                "did I",
                "had I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7fbd78e8c6bf4394a3b2b6784a90873b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wondered what time …………….",
            "description": "In indirect questions the subject goes before the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "was the show starting",
                "was starting the show",
                "the show was starting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f8fe259e0e4641bfa102a06603233cf9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I tried …………… the doctor but my hands were numb.",
            "description": "We can use either an infinitive or an ing form after 'try' to talk about making an effort to do something.",
            "answers": [
                "to call",
                "calling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5e6c23d4f8c34c1cb0c28e83dc4143b7"
        }
    ]
}